I've never had a kettle in my house before.
Yeah, like an iPod in a kettle.
iPod?
The kettle and the idol
Well, it's early days for the radar!
Do you have an announcement to make, Mr. Sakurai?
Yes, I do.
On Sunday, February 19th at Osaka Castle Hall
We'll be performing at the idol festival Gortoo Osaka Girls Cassol!
These are all sorts of items.
I'm sure there will be idols there.
It's an idol festival.
That and Osaka-jo Hall.
I'm happy that I can go to Osaka.
That way.
What are you excited about?
Being able to go near USJ.
I can go near USJ.
That's what I'm looking forward to, right?
I'm sure you know what I'm talking about.
I want to go to USJ. I want to go to USJ.
I'll give it a try.
Isn't that work?
I've been told.
That's fun, isn't it?
Have you ever been to USJ?
No, I haven't.
Please look forward to it.
Lastly, the nighttime guests gave us a present of tea.
Thank you very much.
It is tea from Makinohara.
Shizuoka Prefecture.
Do you know? Shizuoka Prefecture?
Yes, I know it.
It is next to Kanagawa Prefecture. Shizuoka Prefecture.
Shizuoka is not that far away.
Wait a minute.
Shizuoka is actually next door!
You know that?
Don't worry, people don't know that.
It's not that easy to find out!
That's right.
I have friends in Shizuoka.
I thought he was far away.
I had an image of him being very far away.
I wouldn't think that would bother you.
I see.
Sorry. Sorry.
There you go.
Good night.
This is the first time I've ever had this reaction.
By yourself like this.
It's delicious.
Yes, it is.
I'll see you at the end.
This show is over.
Just be cute.
Put on your best smile.
May I have one last word?
Yes, ma'am.
One word.
Power.
Thank you for watching!
This program is about Toshikazu-chan
Kisun-san
Mr. Rin
Osamu Sucker Punch
This program was provided by Aoini-san!
Thank you very much!
Bye-bye!